<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Who shot my leg off?</name>
    <author>Tixiv</author>
    <url>https://github.com/tixiv/WhoShotMyLegOff</url>
    <packageId>Tixiv.WhoShotMyLegOff</packageId>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.5</li>
    </supportedVersions>
<description>
A quality of life mod for Rimworld

Did you ever notice that your colonist had a scar or a missing body part, and you just asked yourself: How did that happen? This mod will solve that problem. Now what happened and when it occurred will be displayed on each Hediff (health condition) forever.

The funny thing is: Rimworld actually already has this feature somewhat built in, since Heddifs already save the log string, and the timestamp when they occurred forever. However the log entry isn't displayed in the Hediff anymore after it has been purged from the battle log of the pawn, which might actually be a game bug or oversight.
The nice thing is that this means the data is already there in savegames, so this mod will also work on injuries that occurred before it was installed!

Additionally to fixing this game oversight, this mod also displays when the Hediff occurred right in the Hediff itself. No need to click to the battle log anymore!

Compatibility:
Absolutely no issues expected. This mod patches only the function that get's the battle log entry on a Hediff. That really shouldn't interfere with anything. The mod is also safe to remove at any time.
</description>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld</downloadUrl>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
